[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
[mortar explosions]
Boy, I feel like an idiot.
I'm showing up with a gun
to an artillery fight.
That's like showing up with a rocket
launcher to a tactical warhead fight.
Of course, I didn't KNOW this
was going to be an artillery fight.
[mortar fire]
Oh, boy.
[explosions]
I don't even want to be here!
They can blow up the
damned... dam... for all I care.
Dammit!
[explosions]
I'm pretty sure this is
unconstitutional.
Even cops aren't allowed to mortar people.
I mean, what happened?
Was there an emergency session
of Congress to vote on bombing me?
Okay, think.
I guess I'll just rush them.
If I stagger my approach,
they should miss.
NO!  I CHANGED MY MIND!
I DON'T WANNA DIE!
[underwater panicking]
SHARK!
OH MY GOD!  ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
[gibbering]
I FEEL SUFFICIENTLY MOTIVATED
TO LEAVE THIS PLACE!
I DON'T NEED YOUR ENCOURAGEMENT!
I SAID I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP!
YOU HAVE NO FAITH IN PEOPLE!
[screams]
[panicking]
BOMBS BAD BOMBS BAD BAD BOMBS BAD!
Okay!  Suppressive fire in,
suppressive fire out!
Do the hokey-pokey and
that's what it's all about!
STOP SHOOTING ME!
I'M NOT THE ENEMY!
GET YOUR HEAD OUT OF THE CLOUDS!
Boy... what's it take to get some
peace and quiet around here?
So... let's assess the situation.
I'm in a damned canyon.
I'm stuck on this damned tower.
What's in this damned room anyway?
It's a damned button.
[machine powers down]
Sounds like that did some damned thing.
So, how am I going to get out of here?
The soldiers blew up the damned bridge,
and that damned shark's
still in the dammed water.
Ah hah!
Maybe he's faking it.
No, I think I got him.
Well, that's one less damned
problem to worry about.
But, how am I going to get up
these damned walls?
I don't see a damned ladder anywhere.
There's no damned steps.
This is a damned mess.
Why did those damned soldiers
blow that up, anyway?
I bet they're trying to cut
the damned power.
That means, all those scientists are going
to get stuck underground in the dark.
Well, that's their damned problem.
Okay, my options look pretty
damned limited this way.
Ehh...
I'll guess I'll just check out
what's around that bend.
Maybe there's a cruise ship
that'll serve me some drinks.
[underwater mumbling]
Okay...
Hey!  There's nothing there at all!
It's a damned dead end!
[underwater mumbling]
The water must be seeping in underground.
That doesn't help me at all!
[growling]
I'm sick of this damned place!
I didn't kill that fish just so I could--
--just so I could take over its job!
Hey...
maybe...
...there's a tunnel.
[underwater "Ah hah!"]
[underwater mumbling]
[gasping]
There's some sort of valve down there.
Maybe I could flood the whole canyon.
That'll at least make me feel better.
[underwater mumbling]
[gasping]
Okay, we can do this.
Air...air is for losers.
[metal groaning]
[underwater grunting]
[underwater panicking]
[gasping]
Haaaa....
Waaaahh.. gaaahhh...
[gasping]
Well...
I'll be damned.
I didn't really think I was going
to do anything like that again.
Okay, let's get down to business.
Does this guy have any money on him?
Or snacks?
This guy doesn't have anything.
Well, don't expect any
fare for Charon from me.
If you're too cheap to keep even
fifty cents in your pocket
before throwing yourself off a dam.
Gotta save your money, right?
This stream better go somewhere.
If it doesn't, I'm going to
have to start an avalanche.
I have explosives.
Okay, big giant wall with no steps.
Not what I want to see.
No...
No...!
[growling]
Why lock that gate?
Who do they think is going to break in?
I'm trying to break OUT.
They think someone's going to sneak in
with a bucket and steal their water?
Ah.
I could fit into one of these pipes.
But, which one?
I'll try this one.
If there's a midget squatting here with
a knife then I'll just go in the other one.
Hm.
Oh, what the hell?
They tricked me AGAIN!
Why have two runoff pipes if the circumference
is exactly the same as the source?
Although, I like how they
added lights here.
That's awfully considerate --and
wasteful-- of them.
I bet maybe someone comes
through here twice a year.  If that.
But, then again, we have a dam.
May as well pimp the tunnels
with extra electricity.
[helicopter blades whirring, mortar fire]
Oh, no...
There's another one?!
Oh, this is going to be a long day.
I'd say I need a surface-to-air missile,
but no one should NEED a
surface-to-air missile.
That should be firmly under
"Wants and Desires."
This is bullshit.